[Music]
Hi, I'm Hayes.
I'm Amelia.
And I'm Reese.
And we're Chi Omega's recruitment chairs.
Welcome to Chi O!
[Music]
Hey, my name is Myers Foxworth,
and I'm this year's Chi Omega president.
We hope you're having a great Greek Day,
and we can't wait to show
you what Tau is all about.
[Music]
Chi Omega is the largest
women's organization
in the world and was established in 1895.
Our chapter was the first at Ole Miss,
and we're proud to say
that Chi Omega Tau is the largest
chapter of Chi O nationally.
Our six founding purposes are
friendship, personal integrity,
service to others, academic
and intellectual pursuits,
campus and community involvement,
and career and personal development.
Chi Omega has been recognized
for academic excellence year after year,
consistently maintaining one
of the highest GPAs on campus.
We encourage our active and new
members to pursue academic excellence
by maintaining an average of a 3.0 GPA.
Here you can see a breakdown
of our dues for the upcoming school year
for active and new members of Chi Omega.
In addition to academic excellence, we also
take pride in our involvement on campus.
To name a few, our members are involved
in the Columns Society, Student Ambassadors,
RebelTHON, Big Event, Student Athletics,
Campus Ministries,
Women's Council and more.
We are so proud to have had
our very own Adya Praveen
get crowned Queen
in the 2025 Homecoming Court.
Throughout the recruitment process, I was
able to see how strong Chi O truly is,
and I knew that it was something
that I wanted to be a part of,
and now it's so crazy because it's
something that I could never live without.
Being here has made me realize that
Chi O truly does last a lifetime.
I could have never imagined how these
past four years could have shaped me,
and it's crazy to think that this is just
the beginning of my own Chi O journey.
[Music]
Hey, PC '26!
I'm Bradley Carter.
And I'm Lucy Huthnance.
And we're your new member educators.
Get ready for the best four years ever!
Come see for yourself!
[Music]
Thank you so much for joining
us for a short glimpse
into what makes life at Chi O
so sweet and so special.
We are so excited for this
week, and we cannot
wait to show you what
Chi O is truly all about.
Before we go, we wanted
to share one more thing
that sets the sisterhood apart:
the Chi O Symphony.
One of the best ways
to describe our sisterhood
is through the words of the Symphony,
which details the ideals each
Chi Omega strives to embody.
It's hard to explain the significance
of our Symphony and exactly
how much it means to us,
so we thought we would just show you.
[Music]